{
    "id": "98a61c7b1cf441a984c089089956a862",
    "title": "Identify The Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The river flows under the bridge.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Simple past",
                "Present perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a55ee12932b4d0983b7602888328870"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will answer his letter tonight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Simple future",
                "Future perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "83ff990cb839451599a41449dd904cd8"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been raining all night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present perfect",
                "Present perfect continuous",
                "Past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf5420f8b9934de2b2e4f27b2885fee7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had finished before he came.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple past",
                "Present perfect",
                "Past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8afdd0f24ec34dde806a09693a5be2c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He takes little pride in his work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Present perfect",
                "Simple past"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "285ff6f34d2440da81ab3b2917045c05"
        },
        {
            "question": "By this time tomorrow, I will have reached my home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple future",
                "Future perfect",
                "Future perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d7fb749a8e0a45daabb9a3d2f0ef3e7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mike is waiting for us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Present continuous",
                "Simple past"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c12aaa9e59d04cfdab65416f802f724a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am hoping to get a raise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Present continuous",
                "Simple past"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c2eeac5070047c99672544b3beff263"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will have plenty of time tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple future",
                "Future perfect",
                "Future continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab7146b5e292426a8bdb014a48b6d626"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have heard a strange story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Present perfect",
                "Present continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ec6bfa7e9984357ae08034d26d7ed92"
        }
    ]
}